# Johanna Baguio

#### Web Developer

a 28-year old Filipina finding my way to the IT industry. I was lucky enough to be given the opportunity and be a graduate of Hack Your Future, where I was able to maximize the resources available for me to reach my maximum potential in both back-end and front-end development. I'm a fast- learner who embraces new challenges, while striving for competence and excellence. Join me as we explore endless possibilities in this rapidly changing world of technology.



Amsterdamvej 14, Copenhagen S, Denmark

f facebook.com/johbaguio

instagram.com/johbaguio

29642002

in linkedin.com/in/johanna-may-baguio-a8aa90174

github.com/johbaguio

### **EDUCATION**

#### Dansk 2 CLAVIS

02/2019 - Present

Copenhagen, Denmark

### **Full Stack Web Development**

Hack Your Future

08/2018 – 06/2019 Copenhagen, Denmark

## Språk Kurs (A1,A2)

Folkeuniversitetet

01/2017 – 05/2017 Drammen, Norway

# Bachelor of Science in Information and Communications Technology

University of San Carlos

06/2008 – 03/2013 Cebu, Philippines

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Frontend Developer

Subit

11/2019 – Present Denmark

Contact: Emil Büchler Seier - +45 26 12 36 99

#### **Au Pair**

#### Cultural Exchange Program

06/2018 – Present Copenhagen, Denmark

Contact: Martin Kaae Glarvig – +45 2323 2130

# **Customer/Technical Service Representative**Convergys Philippines Incorporated

07/2013 - 01/2916

Cebu, Philippines

#### Achievements

- Sales Champion (May, June July, August 2015)
- Top Scorecard Achiever (January June 2015)
- Top Agent Year To Date (2015)
- Customer Service Excellence Awardee (2015)

Contact: Mr. Ronald Sara - 09157595258

## SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Javascripl

Node.is

React

Database

Photoshop

## **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

Fabric of my life (03/2019 - 06/2019) 🗗

Exess Luggage (08/2018 – 09/2018) 🗹

HYF- Quiz (12/2018 - 12/2018) 🗗

HYF-Christmas memory game (12/2018 − 01/2019) 🖸

Ouote Generator (08/2019 – 08/2019) 🗹

### **ORGANIZATIONS**

Hack your Future - Copenhagen (09/2018 – Present)

## **CERTIFICATES**

Hack Your Future (09/2018 - 06/2019)

## **LANGUAGES**

English

Filipino

Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Dansk

Limited Working Proficiency

INUISK

Limited Working Proficiency

## **INTERESTS**

Volleyball

Basketball

Badminton

Adventure

Travelling

Music

Photography